Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 20-CB-1025; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 15)
- 20-CB-1026; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 16)
- 20-CB-1027; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 17)
- 20-CB-1028; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 18)
- 20-CB-1029; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 19)
- 20-CB-1030; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 20)
- 20-CB-1031; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 21)
- 20-CB-1032; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 22)
- 20-CB-1033; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 23)
- 20-CB-1034; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 24)
- 20-CB-1035; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 25)
- 20-CB-1036; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 26)
- 20-CB-1037; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 27)
- 20-CB-1038; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 28)
- 20-CB-1039; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 29)
- 20-CB-1040; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 30)
- 20-CB-1041; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 31)
- 20-CB-1042; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 32)
- 20-CB-1043; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 33)
- 20-CB-1044; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 34)
- 20-CB-1014; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 275, Folder 35)
- 20-CB-1046; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 1)
- 20-CB-1047; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 2)
- 20-CB-1048; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 3)
- 20-CB-1049; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 4)
- 20-CB-1050; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 5)
- 20-CB-1051; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 6)
- 20-CB-1052; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 7)
- 20-CB-1053; Machinists, Local 1518, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 8)
- 20-CB-1054; Electrical Workers Local 340, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 9)
- 20-CB-1055; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 10)
- 20-CB-1056; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 748, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 11)
- 20-CB-1058; Machinists Local 1327, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 12)
- 20-CB-1059; Electrical Workers Local 340, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 13)
- 20-CB-1060; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Local 283, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 14)
- 20-CB-1061; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Local 230, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 15)
- 20-CB-1062; Maritime Union of America, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 16)
- 20-CB-1064; Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 17)
  Novato, California
- 20-CB-1065; Plumbing & Pipe Fitting Local 393, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 18)
- 20-CB-1067; Hotel and Restaurant Employees Local 577, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 19)
- 20-CB-1069; Hotel & Restaurant Local 30, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 20)
- 20-CB-1070; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 468, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 21)
- 20-CB-1071; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 70, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 22)
- 20-CB-1073; Newspaper Guild Local 468, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 23)
- 20-CB-1074; Typographical Union Local 21, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 24)
- 20-CB-1075; Carpenters & Joiners Local 1147, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 25)
  Roseville, California
- 20-CB-1077; Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry Local 246, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 26)
- 20-CB-1078; Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry Local 246, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 27)
- 20-CB-1079; Painters, Decorators and Paperhangers Local 272, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 28)
  Monterey, California
- 20-CB-1081; Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers Local 1053, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 29)
- 20-CB-1082; Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry Local 38, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 30)
- 20-CB-1083; Hotels & Restaurant Employees Local 560, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 31)
- 20-CB-1083; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Local 560, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 32)
- 20-CB-1084; Mailers Union Local 59, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 33)
  Fresno-Clovis, California
- 20-CB-1085; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Local 30, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 34)
- 20-CB-1086; Operating Engineers Local 39, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 35)
- 20-CB-1087; Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Local 6, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 36)
- 20-CB-1090; Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 162, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 37)
- 20-CB-1089; Machinists Local 946, 1963 (Box 276, Folder 38)
- 20-CA-1427; Frederickson and Watson, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  Truckee, California
- 20-CA-1428; Aborigin Lumber Company, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  Fort Bragg, California
- 20-CA-1434; Cadre Industries, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  Los Gatos, California
- 20-CA-1544; Al Schneider, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  Lemoore, California
- 20-CA-1545; Hotel & Restaurant Employees, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  Cincinnati, Ohio
- 20-CA-1465; Brown and Hill, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  King City, California
- 20-CA-1466; Brown and Hill, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 7)
- 20-CA-1489; Dalmo Victor Company, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 8)
  Belmont, California
- 20-CA-1500; Topper Feed Mills, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 9)
- 20-CA-1501; Bartenders and Culinary Workers Local 560, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 10)
- 20-CA-1512; Mar Val Food Stores, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 11)
- 20-CA-1515; Al Schneider, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 12)
- 21-CA-3282; Engineers Limited Pipeline Co., 1959 (Box 277, Folder 13)
- 20-CA-1543; Betty Clyne, 1959 (Box 277, Folder 14)
- 20-CB-1130; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Local 110, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 40)
- 20-CB-1131; Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Local 393, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 41)
- 20-CB-1134; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Local 742, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 42)
- 20-CB-1135; Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers Local 1237, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 43)
- 20-CB-1136; Electrical Workers Local 1245, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 44)
- 20-CB-1137; Retail Clerks International Association Local 1288, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 45)
- 20-CB-1138; Carpenters and Joiners of America 1599, 1963 (Box 277, Folder 46)
- 20-CB-1091; Carpenters & Joiners, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 1)
- 20-CB-1091; Carpenters & Joiners Local 22, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 2)
- 20-CB-1091; Carpenters & Joiners Local 36, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 3)
- 20-CB-1092; Hod Carriers Local 261, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 4)
- 20-CB-1092; Hod Carriers Local 304, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 5)
- 20-CB-1093; Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers Local 431, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  Sonora, California
- 20-CB-1094; Carpenters and Joiners of America Local 1040, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 7)
- 20-CB-1095; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 431, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 8)
- 20-CB-1097; Hotel & Restaurant Local 283, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 9)
- 20-CB-1098; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 856, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 10)
- 20-CB-1099; Machinists Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 11)
- 20-CB-1099; Machinists, International Association Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 12)
- 20-CB-1099; Machinists, Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 13)
- 20-CB-1099; Machinists, Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 14)
- 20-CB-1099; Machinists Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 15)
- 20-CB-1099; Machinists, Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 16)
- 20-CB-1100; Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers Local 510, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 17)
- 20-CB-1101; Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 377, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 18)
- 20-CB-1102; Retail Clerks Local 839, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 19)
- 20-CB-1103; Sheet Metal Workers Local 216, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 20)
- 20-CB-1104; Retail Clerks Local 839, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 21)
- 20-CB-1106; Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers Local 8, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 22)
- 20-CB-1107; Woodworkers of America Local 428, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 23)
- 20-CB-1108; Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Local 447, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 24)
- 20-CB-1109; Sheet Metal Workers' Local 75, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 25)
- 20-CB-1110; Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen Local 115, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 26)
- 20-CB-1111; Retail Clerks International Association Local 1532, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 27)
- 20-CB-1112; Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union Local 6, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 28)
- 20-CB-1113; Machinists, Local 1178, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 29)
- 20-CB-1114; Carpenters and Joiners, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 30)
- 20-CB-1115; Newspaper Guild Local 98, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 31)
- 20-CB-1117; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 304, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 32)
- 20-CB-1119; Carpenters and Joiners Local 266, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 33)
- 20-CB-1120; Printing Pressmen and Assistants Local 5, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 34)
- 20-CB-1123; Carpenters & Joiners of America, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 35)
- 20-CB-1126; Operating Engineers Local 39, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 36)
- 20-CB-1127; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 921, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 37)
- 20-CB-1128; Retail Clerks International Association Local 410, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 38)
- 20-CB-1129; Jewelry Workers Union Local 36, 1963 (Box 278, Folder 39)
- 13-CA-3079; D. L. Clark Candy Co., 1963 (Box 279, Folder 1)
- 13-CA-3081; Sunbeam Corporation, 1963 (Box 279, Folder 2)
- 13-CA-3082; Hotpoint Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 3)
- 13-CA-3076; Senn-Soldwedel, Inc., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 4)
- 13-CA-3077; Davenport Packing Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  Milan, Illinois
- 13-CA-3078; Oppenheimer Casing Co., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 6)
- 13-CA-3075; Century Hardware Corporation, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 7)
- 13-CA-3073; Douglas Motors Corporation, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 8)
- 13-CA-3074; The Kendall Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 9)
- 13-CA-3068; Boynton Cab Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 10)
- 13-CA-3071; Bon Tool & Die Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 11)
  River Grove, Illinois
- 13-CA-3065; Aluminum Company of America, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 12)
- 13-CA-3066; Chicago Refining Corporation, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 13)
- 13-CA-3067; Harnishfeger Corporation, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 14)
  Crystal Lake, Illinois
- 13-CA-3058; Newark Electric Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 15)
- 13-CA-3059; Merchants Motor Freight, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-3062; Sinclair Oil Co., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 17)
- 13-CA-3064; McDowell Truck Lines and Hajer Trucking Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 18)
- 13-CA-3042; F. S. Tiger Company, 1959 (Box 279, Folder 19)
- 13-CA-3047; Dearborn Electronic Laboratory, Inc., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 20)
- 13-CA-3049; Town & Country Heating, Inc., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 21)
- 13-CA-3050; Janeen Art Studio, Inc., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 22)
- 13-CA-3052; Transamerican Freight Lines, Inc., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 23)
- 13-CA-3057; Sprout and Davis Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 279, Folder 24)
- 1-CB-522; Atlantic Fishermen's Union, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 1)
- 1-CB-531; Teamsters Local 671, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 2)
- 1-CB-532; United Shoe Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 3)
- 1-CB-526; Local 82 Carpenters and Joiners, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 4)
- 1-CB-527; Local 251 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 5)
- 1-CB-577; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 6)
- 1-CB-578; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 7)
- 1-CB-580; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 8)
- 1-CB-581; Sayles Independent Union, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 9)
  Saylesville, Rhode Island
- 1-CB-582; Sayles Independent Union, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 10)
- 1-CB-537; Local 348 American Bakery & Confectionery Workers International Union of America, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 11)
- 1-CB-538; Local 348 American Bakery & Confectionery Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 12)
- 1-CB-540; Local 29 Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 13)
- 1-CB-541; Local 477, Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 14)
- 1-CB-542; Local 443 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 15)
- 1-CB-543; Local 443 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 16)
- 1-CB-600; Local 223 Hod Carriers, Building and Common Laborers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 17)
- 1-CB-533; Shoe Workers of America, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 18)
- 1-CB-534; United Shoe Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 19)
- 1-CB-535; Local 348 American Bakery, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 20)
- 1-CB-536; Local 348 American Bakery and Confectionery Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 21)
- 1-CB-544; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 22)
- 1-CB-583; Sayles Independent Union, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 23)
- 1-CB-584; Local 281 Garment Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 24)
- 1-CB-585; United Packinghouse Workers of America Local 11, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 25)
- 1-CB-586; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 26)
- 1-CB-588; Steamfitters & Apprentices Local 644, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 27)
- 1-CB-590; Local 4, Hoisting and Portable Engineers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 28)
  West Newton, Massachusetts
- 1-CB-591; Retail, Grocery & Food Clerks Local 1445, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 29)
- 3-CB-592; Meat Cutters, Food Store, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 30)
  Natick, Massachusetts
- 1-CB-593; Meat Cutters & Butcher Workmen Local 2, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 31)
- 1-CB-594; New Bedford Joint Board of Textile Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 32)
- 1-CB-595; International Union of Electrical Radio & Machine Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 33)
- 1-CB-597; Local Union Local 233 Hod Carriers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 34)
- 1-CB-598; Local 223 Hod Carriers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 35)
- 1-CB-599; United Hatters, Cap and Millinery Workers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 36)
- 1-CB-562; National Maritime Union of America, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 37)
- 1-CB-563; Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers Local 37, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 38)
- 1-CB-564; Teamsters Local 671, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 39)
- 1-CB-565; Local 170 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 40)
- 1-CB-566; Local 170 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 41)
- 1-CB-567; Middlesex District Council, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 42)
- 1-CB-568; Textile Workers Union, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 43)
- 1-CB-569; United Shoe Workers Local 12A, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 44)
- 1-CB-570; Truck Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers Union Local 340, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 45)
- 1-CB-572; Local 624 United Brotherhood of Carpenters & Joiners, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 46)
- 1-CB-573; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 47)
- 1-CB-574; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 48)
- 1-CB-575; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 49)
- 1-CB-576; Assabet Valley Lodge 2199, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 50)
- 1-CB-545; Local 2 Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 51)
- 1-CB-546; Local 108 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 52)
- 1-CB-547; National Maritime Union, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 53)
- 1-CB-548; Carpenters and Joiners Local 885, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 54)
- 1-CB-549; Local 885 Carpenters and Joiners, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 55)
- 1-CB-550; Local 170 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 56)
- 1-CB-551; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 170, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 57)
- 1-CB-552; Local 170 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 58)
- 1-CB-553; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 59)
- 1-CB-554; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 60)
  Local 170 Worcester, Massachusetts
- 1-CB-555; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 170, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 61)
- 1-CB-556; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers Local 170, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 62)
- 1-CB-557; Local 170 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 63)
- 1-CB-558; Local 170 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 64)
- 1-CB-559; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 65)
- 1-CB-560; Winslow Local 431, 1959 (Box 280, Folder 66)
  Waterville, Maine
- 17-CB-219; Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers & Helpers, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 1)
- 17-CB-221; Pipefitters Local 533, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 2)
- 12-CB-655; Broward County District Carpenters & Joiners, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 3)
- 12-CB-708; Longshoremens' Association Local 1759, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 4)
- 12-CB-628; Carpenters and Joiners Local 1685, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 5)
- 10-CB-1412; Steelworkers and its Local 6383, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 6)
- 12-CB-682; Motion Picture Machine Operators Local 511, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 7)
- 12-CB-697; Theatrical, Stage Employees and Motion Picture Machine Operators Local 316, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 8)
- 20-CB-686; Laundry Workers Local 2, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 9)
- 12-CB-693; Iron Workers, Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Local 272, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 10)
- 17-CB-220; Painters, Decorators & Paperhangers, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 11)
  Jackson, Missouri
- 21-CB-2090; Truck Drivers Local 235, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 12)
  Buena Park, California
- 12-CB-661; Carpenters Local 1685, 1959 (Box 281, Folder 13)
- 6-CB-980; Steelworkers Local 1256, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 14)
  Duquesne, Pennsylvania
- 12-CB-724; International Longshoremen's Local 1759, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 15)
- 20-CB-689; Electrical Workers Local 100, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 16)
- 13-CA-3104; Pick-Shapiro Fisheries, Inc., 1963 (Box 281, Folder 17)
- 13-CB-526; Dairy, Food Processing, Food Warehousing and Food Sales Local 158, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 18)
- 13-CB-776; Drivers, Warehouse & Dairy Employees Local 75, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 19)
- 13-CB-773; Hotel and Apartment Hotel Service Workers, 1963 (Box 281, Folder 20)
- 10-CB-1408; Steelworkers, Local 2122, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  Wylam, Birmingham, Alabama
- 6-CB-983; Molders and Foundry Workers Union Local 398, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 2)
- 6-CB-1046; Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers Local 491, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  Connellsville, Pennsylvania
- 10-CB-1417; Steelworkers Local 1466, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 4)
- 10-CB-698; Teamsters Local 402, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 5)
- 10-CB-945; Local 387 Bridge, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 6)
- 10-CB-643; Local 271 Machinists, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 7)
- 10-CB-1416; Teamsters Local 728, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 8)
- 10-CB-986; C. H. Green Local 92 Iron Workers, 1963 (Box 282, Folder 9)
- List of Cases and Statistics for C and R cases, 1963 (Box 283, Folder 1)
- Statistical Report on C and R Cases (Box 283, Folder 2)
- Notes on cases (Box 283, Folder 3)
- Conspiracy in Southern Textiles: Presentation of Textile Workers Union of America, 1967 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  August, New York, New York
- Notes and Statistical Reports on C and R cases (Box 283, Folder 5)
- Statistical Reports on C and R cases and notes (Box 283, Folder 6)
- Region 10 Statistical Reports on C and R cases (Box 283, Folder 7)
- Region 3 Notes and Statistical Reports on C and R cases (Box 283, Folder 8)
  Virginia
- Notes on Cases (Box 283, Folder 9)
- Notes on cases (Box 283, Folder 10)
- Notes on cases (Box 283, Folder 11)
- 21-CB-2180; Teamsters Local 203, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 1)
- 21-CB-2181; Painters Local 48, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  La Mirada and Buena Park, California
- 21-CB-2182; Local 300 Hod Carriers, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 3)
- 21-CB-2183; Electrical Radio Local 1512, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 4)
- 21-CB-2184; Local 80 Theatrical Stage Employees, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  Universal City, California
- 21-CB-2185; Engineers Local 12, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 6)
  Irwindale, California
- 21-CB-2187; Carpenters Local 530, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 7)
- 21-CB-2188; Electrical Workers Local 569, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 8)
- 21-CB-2188; Electrical Workers Local 569, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 9)
- 21-CB-2189; Local 630 Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen & Helpers, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 10)
- 21-CB-2190; Carpenters & Joiners Local 1052, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 11)
- 21-CB-2193; Local 25 Carpenters and Joiners, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 12)
- 21-CB-2194; Hodcarriers, Brick tenders & Common Laborers Local 300, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 13)
- 21-CB-2195; Ventura Typographical Union Local 909, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 14)
- 21-CB-2196; Warehouse, Processing & Distribution Local 26, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 15)
- 21-CB-2197; Theatrical Stage Employees Local 839, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 16)
  Hollywood and Burbank, California
- 21-CB-2199; Building Material & Dump Truck Drivers Local 420, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 17)
- 21-CB-2200; Sheet Metal Workers Local 170, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 18)
- 21-CB-2201; Electrical Workers Local 11, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 19)
- 21-CB-2201; Electrical Workers Local 11, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 20)
- 21-CB-2204; Steelworkers Local 4670, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 21)
- 21-CB-2206; Hod Carriers Local 300, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 22)
- 21-CB-2207; S & E Pipeline Construction, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 23)
- 21-CB-2208; McElroy Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Local 20, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 24)
- 21-CB-2210; Retail Clerks Union Local 770, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 25)
- 21-CB-2213; Wood, Wire & Metal Lathers' Local 252, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 26)
- 21-CB-2217; Local 477 Electrical Workers, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 27)
- 21-CB-2226; Teamsters Local 357, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 28)
- 21-CB-2227; Culinary Workers & Bartenders Local 814, 1963 (Box 284, Folder 29)
- Statistical Reports on C and R cases (Box 285, Folder 1)
  Region 15, New Orleans
- Statistical Reports on C and R cases (Box 285, Folder 2)
  Milwaukee Region 30
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 3)
  Region 21 Los Angeles
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 4)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases, 1963 (Box 285, Folder 5)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 6)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 7)
  Region 26 Memphis
- Statistical Report on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 8)
  Region 8 Cleveland
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 9)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 10)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 11)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 12)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 13)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 14)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases (Box 285, Folder 15)
- Statistical Reports on C and R Cases, 1963 (Box 285, Folder 16)
  Region 18 Minneapolis
- 21-CC-551; Teamsters Local 42, 1963 (Box 285, Folder 17)
- 21-CC-552; Los Angeles Photo Engravers Union No. 32, 1963 (Box 285, Folder 18)
- 21-CC-554; Local 11 Electrical Workers, 1963 (Box 286, Folder 1)
- 21-CC-557; Radio Recording and Television Employees, 1963 (Box 286, Folder 2)
- 21-CA-4977; Treasure-Craft of California, 1963 (Box 286, Folder 3)
- 21-CA-5115; Mrs. Fay's Pies, Inc., 1963 (Box 286, Folder 4)
- 21-CA-4965; Dillingham Ticket Company, 1963 (Box 286, Folder 5)
- 21-CA-4976; Custom Gifts, Inc., 1963 (Box 286, Folder 6)